// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q005: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'To go to work, Ms. Khan needed to rent a car while ------ was being repaired.',
      choices: ['she', 'herself', 'her', 'hers'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['hers'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Most customers ------ have purchased the tablets developed by Protech are very satisfied with the long-lasting batteries.',
      choices: ['which', 'whose', 'who', 'what'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['who'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Visitors to Haswell Systems must ------ identification at the security desk and receive a visitor badge.',
      choices: ['oversee', 'present', 'approve', 'expect'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['present'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'In ------ to requests from local residents, bike lanes have been built on Cooper Street.',
      choices: ['responsive', 'respond', 'responsively', 'response'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['response'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'By expanding into the Southeast Asian market, Telco Creative has been able to more than double its sales ------the past five years.',
      choices: ['among', 'over', 'before', 'onto'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['over'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'To be ------ to apply for that laboratory technician position, you must have at least three years of work experience.',
      choices: ['frequent', 'eligible', 'accurate', 'responsible'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['eligible'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Digital images such as photos and illustrations in this website may not be used ------ permission.',
      choices: ['regarding', 'unlike', 'without', 'following'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['without'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ who pass the first round of online interviews will be invited for an interview at the companyâ€™s headquarters.',
      choices: ['Application', 'Applicant', 'Apply', 'Applicants'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Applicants'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Questions regarding the new reimbursement system should be ------ to Mr. Luis in the accounting department.',
      choices: ['asked', 'coordinated', 'covered', 'directed'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['directed'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Tickets for Carlin Theater are ------ online three months prior to the performance.',
      choices: ['availabilities', 'available', 'availability', 'availably'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['available'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}